{
    "id": "3c4002a259be4e0ab753b074656f58ba",
    "title": "Present Perfect Tense Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We have lived in this city ……………………… fifteen years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "since"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She has not …………………. returned from school.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "yet",
                "just"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Jane has …………………. gone out.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "just",
                "yet"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You have not returned my money …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "already",
                "yet"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "James has ………………….. arrived in London.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "already",
                "yet"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I have ………………….. had a call from your mother.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "just",
                "yet"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She has worked with me ……………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I haven’t seen him …………………. two weeks.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "How ...................................... have you known him?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "long",
                "much"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I have ................................ completed my homework.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "already",
                "yet"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}